<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Docs on</title><link>https://docs.paperd.ink/docs/</link><description>Recent content in Docs on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.paperd.ink/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>1. Getting Started</title><link>https://docs.paperd.ink/docs/software/getting-started/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://docs.paperd.ink/docs/software/getting-started/</guid><description>Arduino IDE Please download the Arduino IDE version 1.x from Arduino&amp;rsquo;s site →.
⚠ To use bitmaps please install Arduino IDE version 1.x, the File System uploader is incompatible with version 2.x. ESP32 Board In the Arduino IDE, go to File &amp;gt; Preferences
Find the Additional Board Manager URLs field to enter the following URL and click OK
https://dl.espressif.com/dl/package_esp32_index.json Open the Arduino IDE and go to Tools &amp;gt; Board &amp;gt; Boards Manager In the Boards Manager, search for ESP32 and install the ESP32 by Espressif Systems board.</description></item><item><title>2. Libraries Used</title><link>https://docs.paperd.ink/docs/software/libraries/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://docs.paperd.ink/docs/software/libraries/</guid><description> 💡 You can go to Tools > Manage Libraries in the Arduino IDE to search and install the latest versions of following libraries. These are some of the common libraries used in the examples. More information about these can be found in the examples github repo.
Adafruit GFX by Adafruit GxEPD by Jean-Marc Zingg GxEPD2 by Jean-Marc Zingg ArduinoJson by Benoit Blanchon JSON Streaming Parser by Daniel Eichhorn</description></item><item><title>3. Home Assistant</title><link>https://docs.paperd.ink/docs/software/home_assistant/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://docs.paperd.ink/docs/software/home_assistant/</guid><description>⚠️ Home Assistant is currently only supported on Paperd.Ink Classic. It can take up to 20 minutes to install Home Assistant, so you might want to have a cup of coffee. Or five. Setting up Home Assistant Visit the Home Assistant installation page and select the appropriate OS/Machine here →. Choose the Home Assistant Operating System method for installation. If you decide to use a different installation method, make sure to install the HA Supervisor to enable the installation of the ESPHome add-on, which is needed to communicate with Paperd.</description></item><item><title>4. Examples</title><link>https://docs.paperd.ink/docs/software/examples/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://docs.paperd.ink/docs/software/examples/</guid><description>Paperdink Arduino Library Examples To get started with the Paperdink library follow the instructions here→ .
Crypto Tracker Track your cryptocurrency investments to see how much you&amp;rsquo;re in the red ;p
https://github.com/paperdink/PaperdInk-Library/tree/main/examples/Crypto_Tracker
Youtube Stats Show off your youtube views and subscribers count
https://github.com/paperdink/PaperdInk-Library/tree/main/examples/Youtube_Stats
Wave A clean dashboard with weather, date and day, up to 11 to-do items. Syncs to-do list with Todoist or Taiga.
https://github.com/paperdink/PaperdInk-Library/tree/main/examples/Wave
Calther Display calendar, date, weather and to-do list synced with Todoist or Taiga.</description></item><item><title>5. Community Contributions</title><link>https://docs.paperd.ink/docs/software/community_contributions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://docs.paperd.ink/docs/software/community_contributions/</guid><description>We are excited to see what you build with paperd.ink. Send an email to prasad@paperd.ink with a link to your project and we will list it here.</description></item><item><title>6. Hardware</title><link>https://docs.paperd.ink/docs/hardware/hardware/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 22:20:38 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://docs.paperd.ink/docs/hardware/hardware/</guid><description>Block Diagram Specifications ESP32-WROOM-32 powerful module FCC/CE Certified WiFi &amp;amp; Bluetooth wireless connectivity to unlock the full potential of paperd.ink Tri-color &amp;amp; monochrome 400x300 px e-paper displays for the 2 variants Merlot and Classic &amp;lt;20uA current consumption in sleep mode means longer battery life and more freedom to create CP2104 USB-UART converter onboard for easy programming and updates MicroSD Card slot for convenient storage of images, files, and more Piezo Buzzer provides notifications and alerts for a more interactive experience 4x Tactile Buttons for user input and control Extension Header for easy interfacing and expansion of capabilities, enabling limitless creativity and hacking possibilities 1900mAh LiPo battery allows you to keep your e-paper projects running without worrying about running out of power Battery Charger circuit to keep it truly wireless Pin Map &amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>7. Classic Vs Merlot</title><link>https://docs.paperd.ink/docs/hardware/comparison/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 22:20:38 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://docs.paperd.ink/docs/hardware/comparison/</guid><description>Classic Vs Merlot Feature Classic Merlot Colors 4 level grayscale Black, White and Red Display resolution 400x300 px 400x300 px Screen size 4.2 inch 4.2 inch Full update time ~ 1 sec ~ 17 sec Partial update time ~ 0.5 sec (Fast partial update) ~ 17 sec (Slow partial update) I/O expander address 0x38 0x38 Deep sleep current (Timer Wakeup) 16uA 17uA Deep sleep current (Button Wakeup) 1.4mA 1.4mA Battery capacity 1900mAh 1900mAh Enclosure color Black + White White + Red SD card tray Yes Yes Type-C Charging/Programming port Yes Yes Ideal Use Cases Calendar, To-Dos, Tracking, etc.</description></item><item><title>8. Assembly</title><link>https://docs.paperd.ink/docs/hardware/assembly/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 22:20:38 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://docs.paperd.ink/docs/hardware/assembly/</guid><description>How to assemble paperd.ink Note: paperd.ink devices do not come with extension headers pre-installed. The above visuals are for representation only.
Enclosure files Github →</description></item></channel></rss>